<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Ma Veille Technologique</title><link>https://rodral.github.io/labveilletech/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Ma Veille Technologique</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://rodral.github.io/labveilletech/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Tech Watch</title><link>https://rodral.github.io/labveilletech/posts/tech-watch/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rodral.github.io/labveilletech/posts/tech-watch/</guid><description>Explanation of the listening system in place Staying updated with the latest technology trends is essential in this era of rapid digital advancement. Different platforms have emerged as reliable sources for accessing, discussing, and sharing up-to-the-minute insights into the world of technology. Here&amp;rsquo;s what platforms I use to keep my finger on the pulse of tech developments.
Medium.com Medium is a trusted source for in-depth perspectives on technology. By connecting directly with tech enthusiasts, industry leaders, and innovators, it offers a wealth of knowledge that spans a wide range of topics.</description></item><item><title>Tiktok Marketing</title><link>https://rodral.github.io/labveilletech/posts/tiktok-marketing/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rodral.github.io/labveilletech/posts/tiktok-marketing/</guid><description>How new marketing strategies are changing the way we consume content and interact with brands TikTok tour guide Roger311, a popular Chinese TikToker, visits a functional beverage factory created by his college senior classmates. The factory boasts a modern design, featuring a colorful entrance with art inspired by the renowned KAWS statues. Roger was impressed with the efforts to create a work environment that rivals those of Silicon Valley companies, and described the factory as a children&amp;rsquo;s playground that was more stylish than his own home.</description></item><item><title>Innovative Learning</title><link>https://rodral.github.io/labveilletech/posts/innovative-learning/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rodral.github.io/labveilletech/posts/innovative-learning/</guid><description>Introduction In recent years, social media has become an increasingly powerful tool for education and learning. One platform that has seen a surge in popularity for education and innovation is Instagram. Instagram has been utilized by educators and influencers to spread knowledge and information, and this trend has been especially prominent in the digital marketing and technology space.
One Instagram page that has gained recognition for its contribution to learning and innovation is @askyourdigitalagency.</description></item><item><title>Complexity</title><link>https://rodral.github.io/labveilletech/posts/complexity/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rodral.github.io/labveilletech/posts/complexity/</guid><description>Introduction Many problems that we encounter in life are either complex or complicated, and it is essential to understand the difference between the two. In this article, we will explore the distinction between complex and complicated problems and the approach one should take to solve each type of problem.
Complex Problems Complex problems are characterized by having many interrelated parts that are difficult to understand and predict. These problems require a different approach compared to complicated problems as they are not easily solved by following a set of instructions.</description></item><item><title>Google Killer</title><link>https://rodral.github.io/labveilletech/posts/google-killer/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rodral.github.io/labveilletech/posts/google-killer/</guid><description>OpenAI&amp;rsquo;s ChatGPT is a highly innovative language model that has the potential to disrupt the search engine industry. In a recent article, &amp;ldquo;Can ChatGPT Kill Google?&amp;rdquo; by Ignacio de Gregorio Noblejas, the author explores the capabilities of ChatGPT and its potential impact on search engines like Google.
ChatGPT&amp;rsquo;s ability to understand and respond to natural language is one of its key strengths. This means that users can interact with the model in a way that feels natural, asking questions in a conversational manner and receiving relevant answers.</description></item><item><title>UX Usefulness</title><link>https://rodral.github.io/labveilletech/posts/ux-usefulness/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rodral.github.io/labveilletech/posts/ux-usefulness/</guid><description>Why Focusing on Usefulness is More Important Than Focusing on User Experience In the era of digital transformation, businesses are consistently trying to distinguish themselves through the creation of unique, user-centered products. The concept of User Experience (UX) has taken center stage as a key to digital success. However, usefulness—fulfilling a user&amp;rsquo;s actual needs—has emerged as an essential consideration that may outweigh UX in terms of creating truly lasting, valuable products.</description></item></channel></rss>